# qnas = questions and answers.
# there are 10 qna sets. Hopefully, more will be added later
qnas = [
    {'results': [{
        'correct_answer': 'Caterpie',
        'incorrect_answers': ['Charmander', 'Pikachu', 'Pidgey'],
        'question': 'What was Ash Ketchum\'s second Pokemon?'
    }]},
    {'results': [{
        'correct_answer': 'The Salamander',
        'incorrect_answers': ['The Dragon Slayer', 'The Dragon', 'The Demon Slayer'],
        'question': 'In "Fairy Tail", what is the nickname of Natsu Dragneel?'
    }]},
    {'results': [{
        'correct_answer': 'Einstein',
        'incorrect_answers': ['Edward', 'Rocket', 'Joel'],
        'question': 'What is the name of the corgi in Cowboy Bebop'
    }]},
    {'results': [{
        'correct_answer': 'Yukine',
        'incorrect_answers': ['Karuha', 'Mineha', 'Mayu'],
        'question': 'In the anime Noragami who is one of the main protagonists?'
    }]},
    {'results': [{
        'correct_answer': 'Osamu Tezuka',
        'incorrect_answers': ['Mitsuteri Yokoyama', 'Takao Saito', 'Yoshiro Tatsumi'],
        'question': 'Who is the author of the manga series "Astro Boy"'
    }]},
    {'results': [{
        'correct_answer': 'Blank',
        'incorrect_answers': ['Immanity', 'Disboard', 'Warbeasts'],
        'question': 'The two main characters of "No Game No Life", Sora and Shiro, together go by what name?'
    }]},
    {'results': [{
        'correct_answer': 'Domino\'s',
        'incorrect_answers': ['Papa John\'s', 'Pizza Hut', 'Sabarro\'s'],
        'question': 'In 2013, virtual pop-star Hatsune Miku had a sponsorship with which pizza chain?'
    }]},
    {'results': [{
        'correct_answer': 'Gainax',
        'incorrect_answers': ['Kyoto Animation', 'Pierrot', 'A-1 Pictures'],
        'question': 'What animation studio produced "Gurren Lagann"'
    }]},
    {'results': [{
        'correct_answer': 'The Porygon Line',
        'incorrect_answers': ['The Pikachu Line', 'The Elekid Line', 'The Magby Line'],
        'question': 'Which Pok√©mon and it\'s evolutions were banned from appearing in a main role after the Episode 38 Incident?'
    }]},
    {'results': [{
        'correct_answer': 'Kaname Chidori',
        'incorrect_answers': ['Teletha Testarossa', 'Melissa Mao', 'Kyoko Tokiwa'],
        'question': 'Who is the main heroine of the anime, Full Metal Panic!'
    }]}
]